question_data = [
    # {"question": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"question": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"question": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"question": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"question": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"question": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"question": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"question": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"question": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"question": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"question": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"question": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"},


    #Added all these new questions
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.", "answer": "False", "not": ["True"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it's entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.", "answer": "False", "not": ["True"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "French is an official language in Canada.", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.", "answer": "False", "not": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.", "answer": "False", "not": ["True"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "answer": "False", "not": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Pluto is a planet.", "answer": "False", "not": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ", "answer": "False", "not": ["True"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.", "answer": "False", "not": ["True"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.", "answer": "False", "not": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Vietnam's national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.", "answer": "False", "not": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "answer": "False", "not": ["True"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.", "answer": "True", "not": ["False"]}
]



